Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Public TV, 253683
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 9, July 23, 1974; ID: 326.0902; 258740 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0902)
    Lisa Marshall - "Visiting with Darlene", Martha Coolidge - "More Than a School," "Old Fashion Woman"
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 10, July 23, 1974; ID: 326.0903; 258741 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0903)
    Cont. Reel #9 (M. Coolidge), Judy Collins & Jill Godmilow - "Antonia"
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 11, July 23-24, 1974; ID: 326.0904; 258742 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0904)
    Cont. Reel #10 (Collins & Godmilow), Fred Becker - "Heros"
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 12, July 24, 1974; ID: 326.0905; 258743 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0905)
    Mitch Black - "No Lies", Erik Barnouw - "Ape & Superape" by Bert Haanstra
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 13, July 24-25, 1974; ID: 326.0906; 258744 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0906)
    Jim Klein & Julia Reichert - "Methadone: an American Way of Dealing", Amalie Rothschild - "Nana, Mom & Me"
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 14, July 25, 1974; ID: 326.0907; 258745 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0907)
    Cont. Reel #3 (A. Rothschild), Dr. Leslie Rubin - "Last Grave at Dimbaza"
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 15, July 25, 1974; ID: 326.0908; 258746 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0908)
    Cont. Reel #14 (L. Rubin), Chris Marker - "Chili," "The Battle of the Ten Million Tons" "Guern", begin end of Rubin, cuts in and out
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 16, July 25-26, 1974; ID: 326.0909; 258747 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0909)
    Daniel Dietrich & Chris Speeth - "Eakins", Final Discussion
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 17, July 26, 1974; ID: 326.0910; 258748 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0910)
  - Public Television Seminar Reel 18, July 26, 1974; ID: 326.0911; 258749 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0911)
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third World Films Reel 1, October 24, 1975; ID: 326.0912; 258750 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0912)
    Auditorium Opening, Discussion Part 1: Harold Weaver.
    Recordist - Anthony Wisdom/Asst. - Victor Mims
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 2, October 24-25, 1975; ID: 326.0913; 258752 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0913)
    Discussion Part 2: Harold Weaver. Discussion led by Pearl Bowser on "Scar of Shame".
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 3, October 25, 1975; ID: 326.0914; 258753 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0914)
    Lecture & Discussion. Pt. 1 - Pearl Bowser on "Independent Black Film Productions. Pt. 2 - Discussion w/Filmmakers. Pt. 3 - Discussion w/Jim Simon.
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 4, 1975; ID: 326.0915; 258755 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0915)
    Currently unavailable.
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 5, October 25, 1975; ID: 326.0916; 258756 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0916)
    Lecture and Discussion w/Donald Boyle cont.
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 6, October 25, 1975; ID: 326.0917; 258758 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0917)
    Day #2 cont. - Minority Programming on Public T.V.
    Jose Garcia - Realidades.
    William Greaves - Black Journal.
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 7, October 25, 1975; ID: 326.0918; 258761 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0918)
    Day #2 Cont. - Minority Programming on Public T.V. Cont.
    Jose Garcia Discussion
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 8, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0919; 258762 (Box 18, Media ID: 326.0919)
    Discussion in Auditorium:
    A. Participants Film
    B. "Last Grave at Dimbaza" Discussion w/Nana Mahumo
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 9, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0920; 258783 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0920)
    Last Grave at Dimbaza - Nana Mahomo
    The Latin American Film: A New Perspective - Jaime Barrios and Rodolpho Brouillon
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 10, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0921; 258784 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0921)
    Discussion in Auditorium: "The Latin American Perspective" - Jaime Barrios and Rodolpho Browillon
    Recordist - Anthony Wisdom/Asst.- Victor Mims
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 11, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0922; 258785 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0922)
    Discussion: Sadie Lynch - Lost Control, Anthony Chancy - Oh My God
    Recordist - Anthony Wisdom/Asst. Victor Mims
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 12, October 26, 1975; ID: 326.0923; 258786 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0923)
    Bill Gunn
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 13, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0924; 258787 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0924)
    Clayton Riely and Bill Gunn
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 14, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0925; 258789 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0925)
    Discussion: Black Distribution, tape inaudible
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 15, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0926; 258790 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0926)
    Discussion: tape inaudible
  - International Film Seminar Black and Third-World Films Reel 16, October 27, 1975; ID: 326.0927; 258791 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0927)
    Closing [remarks]
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel A, July 11, 1975; July 12, 1975; ID: 326.0928; 258792 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0928)
    Cliff Crawford - "The D & R", James Chen - introducing "The Red Flag Canal", M. Rubbo - "Bates Car: Sweet as a Nut", Mirra Bank - "Yudie"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel B, July 13, 1975; ID: 326.0929; 258793 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0929)
    J. Chen introduction and discussion of "Sandstone Gulch"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel C, July 13, 1975; ID: 326.0930; 258794 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0930)
    G. Stoney: NYU Student Films, Colin Young: Observational Cinema, A. Lomax: "Dance and Human History"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel D, July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0931; 258796 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0931)
    A. Lomax: Choreometric Study Films, C. Young: Observational Film - "Juvenile Liason Scheme"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel E, July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0932; 258797 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0932)
    cont. C. Young: Observational Film - "Juvenile Liason Scheme"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 1, July 10, 1975; July 11, 1975; ID: 326.0933; 258799 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0933)
    M. Rubbo - "Waiting for Fidel", Pacific Street Film Collective - "Frame-Up"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 2, July 11, 1975; ID: 326.0934; 258800 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0934)
    cont. Pacific Street Film Collective - "Frame-Up", James Chen - "The Red Flag Canal", Yuan-Tsung Chen
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 3, July 11, 1975; July 12; 1975; ID: 326.0935; 258801 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0935)
    Susumo Hani - "TVTV Nippon", B. Van Dyke - "Working Mothers"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 4, July 12, 1975; ID: 326.0936; 258802 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0936)
    cont. B. Van Dyke - "Working Mothers", C. Weill and A. Slesin - "The Other Hald of the Sky"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 5, July 12, 1975; July 14, 1975; ID: 326.0937; 258803 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0937)
    D. Brittain - "Bethune" and "Dreamland", S. Hani - "Children Who Draw"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 6, July 14, 1975; July 15, 1975; ID: 326.0938; 258804 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0938)
    S. Hani - "Mio", C. Young - "Mau Mau"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 7, July 15, 1975; ID: 326.0939; 258805 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0939)
    D. Leiterman - "One More River", Joyce Campbell - "Companero" and "Dreams & Nightmares"
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 8, July 15, 1975; July 16, 1975; ID: 326.0940; 258806 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0940)
    cont. Joyce Campbell - "Companero" and "Dreams & Nightmares", W. Van Dyke - Final Discussion
  - PBS Seminar 1975 Reel 9, July 16, 1975; ID: 326.0941; 258807 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0941)
    cont. W. Van Dyke - Final Discussion
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 1, May 23, 1976; May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0942; 258808 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0942)
    B. Van Dyke, Bill Sloan, D. A. Pennebaker - Opening Remarks D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction of films Bill Miles and Dick Adams - Discussion of "Men of Bronze"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 2, May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0943; 258809 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0943)
    L. Kammerling and Sarah Elder - discussion "Space: A Visual Experience" and "On the Spring Ice"
  - Public Television Seminar 1976 Reel 3, May 24, 1976; ID: 326.0944; 258810 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0944)
    cont. L. Kammerling and Sarah Elder - discussion "Space: A Visual Experience" and "On the Spring Ice".
    Mary Lampson - discussion of "Lovejoy's Nuclear War" and "Underground"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 4, May 24, 1976; May 25, 1976; ID: 326.0945; 258811 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0945)
    cont. Mary Lampson - discussion of "Lovejoy's Nuclear War" and "Underground"
    B. Kopple discussion of labor films: "Blow for Blow," "McKaysville," and "Coal Miners"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 5, May 25, 1976; ID: 326.0946; 258813 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0946)
    Discussion of animated films - Eli Noyes, Robert Breer, George Griffin, John Canemaker, Hart Perry
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 6, May 25, 1976; May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0947; 258818 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0947)
    Mirra Bank - Discussion of "Pass Me that Club Please", B. Van Dyke - Introduction of "Dagguerotypes", K. Griffith - Introduction of "Edmund Kean",
    D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction of Performance Films, Doris Chase - "Dance 11", Discussion of "Sound of One"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 7, May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0948; 258820 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0948)
    D. A. Pennebaker - Introduction to "Monterey Pop" sequence, Susan Woll, Victoria Hochberg, Amy Greenfield, Ed Ernshwiller - Discussion of Performance films, P. Montgomery - Introduction of "Grassroots", J. Schott and J. Vaughn - Introduction of "Commercial Television: Let's Make a Deal"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 8, May 26, 1976; ID: 326.0949; 258822 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0949)
    John Schott and Jeff Vaughn - discussion of "Commercial Television Let's Make a Deal", D. A. Pennebaker - discussion of "Grassroots", Warrington Hudlin - introduction and discussion of "Black at Yale", Introduction and discussion of "Potlatch", Introduction - Eva Brown home movies
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 9, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0950; 258823 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0950)
    Introduction to science films - Pennebaker, Introduction and discussion of "Crossroads", Introduction and discussion of "Curve Filling Space" with Bill Hansard
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 10, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0951; 258824 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0951)
    Discussion "Organism" with Hilary Harris, Discussion "The Clinton Special" with M. Ondaatje, Discussion "Circle in the Fire" with V. Nunez
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 11, May 27, 1976; ID: 326.0952; 258825 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0952)
    Introduction and discussion of "Family Focus" by Ed and Carol Emshwiller, Discussion of "Tea Party by Susan Woll
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 12, May 27, 1976; May 28, 1976; ID: 326.0953; 258826 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0953)
    Introduction and discussion of "Suddenly an Eagle" and "The Pursuit of Happiness" with K. Griffith, Discussion of "Dirty Books," "Menstruation," and Liz Suados work in progress with Linda Feferman, Closing session
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1976 Reel 13, May 28, 1976; ID: 326.0954; 258827 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0954)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 1, May 29, 1977; ID: 326.0955; 258828 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0955)
    Opening remarks by Bill Sloan and Jay Ruby, Chip Blumberg Ant Farm videotapes (continued Reel 2)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 2, May 29, 1977; May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0956; 258829 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0956)
    Continuation Chip Blumberg, Walter Parkes - "California Reich"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 3, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0957; 258830 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0957)
    Discussion Japanese relocation camps films, Marianne Lamour "Golden Triangle" (continued on Reel 4)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 4, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0958; 258831 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0958)
    Continuation M. Lamour, Alfonso Beato "Puerto Rico - Paradise Invaded"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 5, May 30, 1977; ID: 326.0959; 258832 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0959)
    Barbara Margolis "On the Line"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 6, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0960; 258833 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0960)
    Paul O'Dell "Oklahoma Posse", Jim Klein, Miles Mogulescu, Julia Reichart - "Union Maids" (continued Reel 7)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 7, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0961; 258834 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0961)
    Continuation "Union Maids", Grant Munro on films by Caroline Leaf, Alfred Guzzetti "Family Portrait Sittings" (continued on Reel 8)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 8, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0962; 258835 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0962)
    Alfred Guzzetti "Family Portrait Sittings" (continued from Reel 7)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 9, May 31, 1977; ID: 326.0963; 258836 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0963)
    Julie Gustafson "The Politics of Intamicy", Alan and Susan Raymond "Police Tapes"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 10, June 1, 1977; ID: 326.0964; 258837 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0964)
    Discussion of "My Childhood", John Reilly and Julie Gustafson "Giving Birth"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 11, June 1, 1977; ID: 326.0965; 258838 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0965)
    Steina and Woody Vasulka on their video work, Elaine Baly and Bill Stephens "Uganda Tapes" (continued on Reel 12)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 12, June 1, 1977; June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0966; 258839 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0966)
    Continuation of Stephens and Baly on Uganda, Perry Miller Adato "Georgia O'Keeffe", Jay Ruby "The History Book" and "The Incredible Bread Machine"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 13, June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0967; 258840 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0967)
    Thom Anderson "Eadweard Muybridge - Zoopraxographer", Anita Thatcher 'Homage to Magritte", General discussion "Brain Surgery" and "Brain...Dynamite..."
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 14, June 2, 1977; ID: 326.0968; 258841 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0968)
    Continuation of Reel 13, David Halpern and Jim Guttman "Hollywood on Trial"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 15, June 3, 1977; ID: 326.0969; 258842 (Box 19, Media ID: 326.0969)
    Linda Feferman "The Girl with the Incredible Feeling", Summary Erik Barnouw, Final discussion (continued on Reel 16)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1977 Reel 16, June 3, 1977; ID: 326.0970; 258843 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0970)
    Final discussion (continued from Reel 15)
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 1, May 28, 1978; ID: 326.0971; 258844 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0971)
    Opening remarks by Jay Ruby and Jack Willis Discussion on "Aguirre"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 2, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0972; 258845 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0972)
    Discussion, Dick Rogers on "Elephants" Discussion, "Banks and the Poor"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 3, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0973; 258846 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0973)
    Discussion with Judy Irola on "Prarie Fire" and Saul Landau on "The Case Officer" Discussion with Dick Moore on "Lose Just the Same"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 4, May 29, 1978; ID: 326.0974; 258847 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0974)
    Discussion with Geri Ashur on "Stella and Me" Discussion with Saul Landau on "Que Hacer"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 5, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0975; 258848 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0975)
    Discussion Tom Palazzolo on "Hot and Nasty" and Judy Irola on "Self-Health"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 6, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0976; 258849 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0976)
    Discussion with Robert Van Lierop on "O Povo Organizado" Discussion with Anne Bohlen on "Babies and Banners"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 7, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0977; 258850 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0977)
    Informal discussion on PBS decision making process Discussion with R. Kramer on "Class Struggle in Portugal"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 8, May 30, 1978; ID: 326.0978; 258851 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0978)
    Jill Godmilow discussing "Popovich Brothers"
  - Public Broadcast Seminar 1978 Reel 9, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0979; 258852 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0979)
    Discussion with Rafael Corkidi on "Pafnucio Santo" Discussion with Pacific St. Film Collective on "Red Squad" (continued on Reel 10)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 10, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0980; 258907 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0980)
    Continuation of discussion with Pacific Street Film Collective Discussion with Phil Parmet on "LeRoy the Magician" and Roy Campanella on "Pass/Fail"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 11, May 31, 1978; ID: 326.0981; 258908 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0981)
    Discussion with Patricio Guzman, Pedro Chaskel, and Rodolfo Broullon on "The Battle of Chile" (continued on Reel 12) (beginning of Guzman's explanation of his methodology is lost due to technical problem)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 12, May 31, 1978; June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0982; 258909 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0982)
    Continuation of Reel 11 - Discussion of "The Battle of Chile" (comments by P. Guzman on methodology) Discussion with Kit Laybourne and Mickey Lemle on "Mediaprobe"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 13, June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0983; 258910 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0983)
    Discussion with Bill Yahraus on "Home Boys" Discussion with D. Keller and C. Light on "Last Resort"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 14, June 1, 1978; ID: 326.0984; 258911 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0984)
    Discussion with Joel Freedman on "Broken Treaty..." Discussion on "We're Not the Jet Set"
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 15, June 1, 1978; June 2, 1978; ID: 326.0985; 258912 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0985)
    Discussion on "We're Not the Jet Set" (continued from Reel 14) Discussion with Dezso Magyar on "Punitive Expedition" Final discussion with summary of the week by Eric Barnouw (continued on Reel 16)
  - Public Television Seminar 1978 Reel 16, June 2, 1978; ID: 326.0986; 258913 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0986)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 1, May 28, 1979; ID: 326.0987; 258914 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0987)
    Opening discussion with Mitch Block - Speeding and Alain [Tanners] films
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 2, May 28, 1979; ID: 326.0988; 258915 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0988)
    Opening discussion with Mitch Block (continued from Reel 1)
    Jonathan Lewis - Before Hindsight
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 2A, [May 28, 1979]; ID: 326.0989; 258916 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0989)
    Discussion of Northern Ireland with Jon Lewis (continued from Reel 2)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 3, May 28, 1979; May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0990; 258917 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0990)
    Jonathan Lewis discussion (continued from Reel 2 and Reel 2A)
    Faith Hubley - The Carousel of Life
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 4, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0991; 258918 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0991)
    Sonntag
    Neils - Peter Rudolph
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 5, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0992; 258920 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0992)
    Niels Peter - Sonntag (continued from Reel 4), Anita Thatcher, Dick Adams
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 6, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0993; 258922 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0993)
    Eckhardt Stein - Night Hawks
    Bob Lowler, Chris Banford, Jim Morton - Reflections
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 7, May 29, 1979; ID: 326.0994; 258923 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0994)
    Bob Lowler, Chris Bamford, Jim Morton - Reflections
    Jan Krawitz, Thomas Ott, Ross Lowell
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 8, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0995; 258924 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0995)
    Ira Woll, Roland Joffe
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 9, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0996; 258925 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0996)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 10, May 30, 1979; ID: 326.0997; 258926 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0997)
    Barry Braverman, James Kennedy - [Doctoring]
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 11, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.0998; 258927 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0998)
    George Griffin
    Joel Gold, Maxi Cohen
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 12, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.0999; 258928 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.0999)
    Joel Gold, Maxi Cohen,
    Richard Harkness - inside San Quentin
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 13, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.1000; 258929 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1000)
    Richard Harkness (continued from Reel 12)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 14, May 31, 1979; ID: 326.1001; 258931 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1001)
    Yolando MacShane discussion
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 15, ID: 326.1002; 258932 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1002)
    Yolanda MacShane - Public TV and Independents discussion
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 16, May 31, 1979; June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1003; 258933 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1003)
    Yolanda MacShane - discussion of Public TV and Independents (continued from Reel 15)
    Jim Day - discussion of Nixon Film
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 17, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1004; 258934 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1004)
    Jim Day - discussion of Nixon Film (continued from Reel 16)
    Wrap up
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 18, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1005; 258935 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1005)
  - Public Television Seminar 1979 Reel 19, June 1, 1979; ID: 326.1006; 258936 (Box 20, Media ID: 326.1006)
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 1, June 1, 1980; ID: 326.1007; 258937 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1007)
    Introduction by Jay Ruby
    Programmers intro: Jaime Barrios, Alfred Guzzetti, Ralph Maradiaga, George Horsecapture, David Lacy
    Barrio's intro plus house intro
    Film: El Super
    Discussion Leon Ichasco, Manuel Arce also Jaime Barrio
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 2, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1008; 258956 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1008)
    Films: Los Venditos- Luis Ruis
    Campaign Against Racism
    Stuart Hall
    Discussion: Luis Ruis, Mike Fentiman also Davis Lacy, Ralph Maradiaga
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 3, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1009; 258957 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1009)
    "56 1/2 Howard St" plus "Mission Hill and the Miracle of Boston"- R. Broadman discussion with Richard Broadman and Alfred Guzzetti
    Films: Listen Curacas
    The Price we Paid Raymond Young
    discussion: Raymond Young, George Horsecapture, Jaime Barrio
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 4, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1010; 258958 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1010)
    Continues from Tape 3
    Raymond Young's The Price we Paid
    Films Italiamerican Scorcese, Simplimente Jenny Helena Ladd, discussion: Helena Ladd, Jaime Barrio, Alfred Guzzetti
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 5, June 2, 1980; ID: 326.1011; 258959 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1011)
    TRT: 00:63:00
    Continues from Tape 4
    Discussion by Helena Ladd, Simplimente Jenny
    Transmagnification Dambamuality, Ronald Gray, Killer of Sheep, Charles Burnett
    Currently Available.
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 6, June 2-3, 1980; ID: 326.1012; 258960 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1012)
    TRT: 00:51:00
    Continues from Tape 5: Killer of Sheep, Charles Burnett
    Images- Great Movie Massacre, We Remember by Raymond Yakeleya, George Horse Catcher (June 3rd)
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 7, June 3, 1980; ID: 326.1013; 258961 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1013)
    "Agueda Martinez" Moctezuma Esparza, discussion also with Ralph Maradiaga
    We are Workers, Antonnio Parra
    Discussion with Antonnio Parra and Ralph Maradiaga, Raquel Ortiz
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 8, June 3, 1980; ID: 326.1014; 258962 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1014)